http://www.hoopscooponline.com/privacy-policy/

Published by The HOOP SCOOP, Inc., P.O. Box 37122, Louisville, KY 40233
Email Address: hoopscooponline@msn.com | Phone: (502) 500-4667
All rights reserved - Copyright 2016
A national recruiting web site and scouting service providing analysis, rankings, and coverage of grassroots basketball since 1983
Privacy Policy
Last updated: (1/1/2020)
The Hoop Scoop INC (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates https://www.hoopscooponline.com (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
This Privacy Policy only applies to The Hoop Scoop INC Services and not to the practices of companies that The Hoop Scoop INC does not own or control, including operators of Web sites that Users may visit before, during, or after visiting the Site, and the owners or publishers of the documents, advertisements, or postings and other products (collectively, the “Publications”) Users download, review, or otherwise access.
We use your information only for improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. If you use this site you explicitly agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time of your use. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the Calhisports.com site.
Information Collection And Use
You can browse the hoopscooponline.com web site at anytime without revealing any personal information about yourself. There are, however, several areas on our web site where we collect personal information from you on a voluntary basis. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, email address, or credit card that is not otherwise publicly available (“Consumer PII” or “PII”). This information helps us serve you better by enabling us:
to process and fulfill your requests for products and services
to solicit your opinions and other feedback
to conduct research
to customize the advertising and content you see
to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients
We may collect personal information at the following times:
when you register to receive communications from this website or any website owned by the owner of hoopscooponline.com.
when you seek information or apply for products and services offered through this website or any website owned by the owner of hoopscooponline.com.
when you enter promotions or sweepstakes offered by this website or any website owned by the owner of hoopscooponline.com.
when you provide personal information to us through feedback, survey, or other forms hosted on this site or any website owned by the owner of hoopscooponline.com.
when you apply for a job with hoopscooponline.com.
Information Collection of California Minors
Calif. Bus. & Prof. Code §§ 22580-22582, California's Privacy Rights for California Minors in the Digital World Act, also called the "eraser" bill, permits minors to remove, or to request and obtain removal of, content or information posted on an Internet Web site, online service, online application, or mobile application. It also prohibits an operator of a Web site or online service directed to minors from marketing or advertising to minors specified products or services that minors are legally prohibited from buying. The law also prohibits marketing or advertising certain products based on personal information specific to a minor or knowingly using, disclosing, compiling, or allowing a third party to do so.
Hoopscooponline.com publicly displays information about student-athletes 13 years of age or older for the use of profiling their athletic attributes to Site users and/or subscribers. Users, any other Website or third party, shall not use this information for any other purpose. Minors, or their parents/guardians, can request the removal of their profile at any time by emailing us at ronlocc1977@yahoo.com. For more information on Calif. Bus. & Prof. Code §§ 22580-22582, CLICK HERE
Terms Of Use
You may use the Site only for lawful purposes and in accordance with the following Terms of Use. For more information, please see our Terms And Conditions Page. You agree not to use the Website:
in any way that violates any applicable federal, state, local or international law or regulation (including, without limitation, any laws regarding the export of data or software to and from the US or other countries);
for the purpose of exploiting, harming or attempting to exploit or harm minors in any way by exposing them to inappropriate content, asking for personally identifiable information or otherwise;
to send, knowingly receive, upload, download, use or re-use any material which does not comply with our Privacy Policy;
to transmit, or procure the sending of, any advertising or promotional material, including any junk mail, chain letter or spam or any other similar solicitation;
to collect, use and/or disclose personally identifiable information in violation of, (a) these Terms of Use or our Privacy Policy and/or (b) applicable law, including, without limitation, Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA);
to impersonate or attempt to impersonate The Hoop Scoop INC, a Hoop Scoop employee, another user or any other person or entity (including, without limitation, by using e-mail addresses or screen names associated with any of the foregoing);
to engage in any other conduct that restricts or inhibits anyone’s use or enjoyment of the Site, or which, as determined by us, may harm The Hoop Scoop INC or users of the Site or expose them to liability.
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze user data. We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials.
Depending on how you want to be set up, Cookie declaration and consent should be controlled by Cal-OPPA/GDPR and can be turned off with some controlling software. Can work with you on an approach
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
The Hoop Scoop INC uses cookies. Cookies are small text files that can be used by websites to make a user's experience more efficient. We use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyze Site traffic. We also share information about your use of our Site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services. The law states that we can store cookies on your device if they are strictly necessary for the operation of this site. For all other types of cookies we need your permission. This Site uses different types of cookies. Some cookies are placed by third party services that appear on our pages.
Intellectual Property Rights
The Site and its entire contents, features and functionality (including but not limited to all information, software, text, displays, images, video and audio, and the design, selection and arrangement thereof), are owned by The Hoop Scoop INC, its licensors or other providers of such material and are protected by United States and international copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret and other intellectual property or proprietary rights laws.
Legal Protection
We reserve the right to disclose your Consumer PII, as required, to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, judicial proceedings, court orders, or legal process, and will establish or exercise our legal rights and defend against legal claims at our discretion. We will share, without notice to you, all information we possess in response to court orders, subpoenas and to comply with government investigations. At our discretion we will share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of The Hoop Scoop INC’s Terms of Use or as otherwise required by law.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100 percent secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online and protect your information offline. Only employees or contractors who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. If you have any questions about the security of hoopscooponline.com, or need to contact us if you suspect a security breach, please e-mail us at james@jameskerti.com.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of (1/1/2020) and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our Site.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please visit our Contact US page.
Login
Username
Password
Remember Me
Lost PasswordSubscribe Now! One Year Fan Subscription to The HOOP SCOOP, including a digital copy of How To Get Get Recruited by Clark Francis: $100
One Year NCAA Coaches Subscription to The HOOP SCOOP: $499
The HOOP SCOOP Online Archives The HOOP SCOOP Online Archives
Search for:
Privacy Policy · Terms & Conditions
© 2020 Clark Francis
